

PHAM NGUYEN KIM NGAN

Junior Accountant



0852.673.838



phamnkimngan279@gmail.com



District 8, Ho Chi Minh City



www.linkedin.com/in/kim-ngân-3745a4282

EDUCATION

UEH University

2020-2024

Bachelor of Finance and Banking

Programme of Finance Advanced Programme in English GPA: 8.24/10

SAPP Acedemy

2023 - Current

ACCA (The Association of Chartered Certified Accountants)

3 modules of ACCA studied (F2, F3, F7)

SKILLS

Technical (Intermediate):

- Microsoft Office: Word, Excel,
 PowerPoint, (or Docs, Sheet, Form...).
- Design: Canva , Capcut.

Soft skills:

- Communication.
- Problem-solving.
- Teamwork.
- Time management.
- Leadership.

LANGUAGE

English - TOEIC: 675/990

CERTIFICATES

IC3 (The Internet and Computing Core Certificate): GS5.

ABOUT ME

I am a logical thinker with strong management skills, adaptability, and resilience under pressure. Proactively seeks growth opportunities and embraces challenges with enthusiasm. Combines academic knowledge and practical experience to contribute effectively to the company's development.

WORK EXPERIENCE

NAMI TECHNOLOGY JOINT STOCK COMPANY

2022 - Current

Data Quality Assurance

- Quality/quantity validation of processed data based on project standards.
- Reporting risks from data validation to project management.
- Working with stakeholders to ensure data validation processes meet the requirements of each project.

Data Project Assistant

- Recruit and train 'collaborators' to fit in the given task.
- Manage the workflow between superiors and subordinates to finish the project in time.
- Coordinate project tasks such as human resources, equipment preparation, and related documentation (guidelines, meetings, etc.) as requested by the project manager.
- Monitor and report project progress to the project manager.
- Handle/evaluate arising issues and risks.
- Ensure standards and requirements are met by conducting quality assurance checks of the data.

SAIGON THUONG TIN COMMERCIAL JOINT STOCK BANK (SACOMBANK) Aug 2023 - Nov 2023

Credit Expert Intern

- Working in the sales department.
- Assisting customers in opening credit cards.
- Appraising assets for loans.

RESEARCH EXPERIENCE

Scientific research

Recognized research topic at the Festival of Student Scientific Research in the fields of Economics - Law - Urban Development 2021: Integrated Research - Research for All.

Intenrship report

The topic scored 9.8/10.